자막분리: 아뜨(Trademark) (2010-10-03)
JUNG Jae-young
Love is talking a walk itogether at dawn
LEE Na-young
Any one who has held hands
while walking a wooded path
will know
that love is the
greatest thing in the world
It's a forkball
Oh, sorry
Try to stay healthy
I may not come
to your games anymore
So don't push
yourself too hard
Oh, sure
Let's break up
Please
Let's end it now
Hey
Get lost
Just get out of my sight
Hey
You said you love me?
What a load of crap
Why the hell did you
call me out here, anyway?
You can do it
over the phone, huh?
You want anything else?
Oh, you bought me this
now you want it back?
Who the hell wears
corduroy now anyway?
Shit, you women
are all the same!
Shit!
What are you waiting for?
You want me to
chase you off?
Fuck off!
Shit, just leave!
Okay...
I suppose It's for the best
Bye
it wasn't love this time either
I always think that it is
But sooner or later
I find out It's not
I haven't experienced love yet
Not even first love
These tedious nosebleeds
always come when I'm alone
It's 2 o'clock
Time to go to the doctor's
My head's photo is
in black and white
It's the heart
I'm worried about
Oh, so that's the heart
No, those are the lungs
The heart's here
This shouldn't be like this
That's black and white too
It's all black and white
From here it looks
like I'm pigeon-chested
That's not the problem
There are two
kinds of tumors
Malignant ones
and gentle ones
But Mr. DONG
your tumor is malignant
Look here
This here's like that
it shouldn't be like that
If this turns out like that
it'll be dangerous
And as you see
It's already like that
Look at this
It's already moved up here
How did that happen?
It's moving all over
it shouldn't be doing that
What do we do?
Yes?
Oh, It's me
It's September now
I've three months
if I'm lucky
so I won't see next year
My head is strange
It's black and white
and malignant to boot
I'll go have a drink
It's usually like that
People who suddenly
lose next year go drinking
Hey, It's our outfielder
Why are you alone today?
I've always come alone
is that so?
Hello
is your shoulder okay?
Don't play outfield
You should pitch
Pitching is cool
You were so famous in high school
DONG Chi-sung, pitcher!
Throwing from the right
hitting from the left, huh?
A 6-time
Phoenix Cup winner
with MVP and Pitching awards...
The air's no good here
You could catch a disease
from this air
Lung cancer, malignant...
You're awake
Can you see?
The bartender
Why am I here?
Can't even hold your liquor
You brought me here?
You think I followed you?
I'm heavy, how did
you get me here?
I folded you and
put you in a box Why?
You don't even remember
Why'd you drink so much
If you can't hold liquor
But for a sleeping drunk guy
you look really sweet
You don't snore or
flail around
You have no bad mannerisms
I'd never have guessed it
I'll go now
I paid for the room
pay me back later
The wind...
I discovered three things today
that other people have
and I don't
I have no first love
I have no next year
I have no bad mannerisms
Hey, I've never seen that before
It's new, it isn't sweet
It's selling well
I met that guy
Right, you said he's
a regular customer
Yeah
But, this time...
Did you talk to him?
Yeah
Two words?
A bit more than usual
But, we...
Hey, this is great
This'll sell well
Yesterday
that guy and
I went to a hotel
We're just about all here
We'll start this
month's meeting
The leader of our online group
ID 'Pink Mask,'
will speak first
Here we go!
What the hell's
he thinking out there?
Let's go!
Hey!
What's with you?
Aren't you gonna catch it?
What's the point?
What did that punk say?
Have you gone crazy?
Yeah I'm crazy, so what?
Today's confessional postcard
is from a woman in Heukseok-dong
with the lD 'Writing Princess'
He cried today
The first time I saw it
What could cause such a
good-spirited person to cry so?
And he drank yesterday too
It's the first time
I ever saw him drink
And wouldn't you
know it...
This person who never drinks...
after not even three shots
started shouting about
his b&w head and heart
and then passed out
First I took him to a hotel
For me to lift and carry
a man of his size
was not easy
So I had to put him in a box
In the room
I just stared at him vacantly
He didn't snore
or move around
I don't know if
he could tell I was there
There was so much
I wanted to say
and so much I wanted to hear
But with the words
all stuck in my throat
all I could say was
You have no bad mannerisms
That was it
He seemed some what
annoyed at my comment
Waking up to a strange woman
talking about him that way
He seemed offended
Why does nothing
come out the way I wish?
His sad face keeps
coming to my mind
Is there any way I can
make him feel better?
He said he lost his phone...
What's your problem?
Why are you doing this?
Are you playing with me?
I think this story deserves
a mobile phone, huh?
That's right
but what do you think?
Is this love?
It could be one-sided love
or it may just be compassion
Seems like compassion to me
Anyway, Miss Writing Princess
we'll send you
a mobile phone
We hope that next time you can
cheer him up and speak better
I wanted to
give you that present
The mobile phone
from the station
You don't have one
Here's the hotel fee
is that right?
- That's $5 too much
- What do you think I am?
Keep it
You need shampoo?
I heard the news
About you and your girlfriend
I know how you feel
Still, not catching the ball
won't change anything
You think that'll
get you points?
I got a call from
the majors
From tomorrow
you'll start pitching again
Last chance
Just for get everything
and take the mound
Forget your mistake that day
it wasn't your fault
Of course it will be hard
but just forget that day
The most dramatic
moments in
baseball occur
in the 9th inning
And 9 times out of 10
It's due to the
winning team
Dramatic moments come
in two varieties
The first is when someone
excels like crazy,
the second is when
some crazy fool screws up
Strike!
On that day we had a moment
of the second type
thanks to me
Nice pitch!
Let's wrap this up!
in that wild and
deafening stadium
I still can't understand how
I was able to hear her voice
You damned moron!
If we break up like this
you'll go meet someone new
How long will it last?
A week? A month?
And you'll meet
someone else again
But then you'll discover again
it wasn't love
That's the way you are!
Your love is too weak
Just die!
If you say you love me
then you can die with me
If we die that way, then the love
we wanted will come true
Don't let go of love
you fool!
That most dramatic moment
in baseball was
of my making
For the first time, I was
on the sports papers' front page
A Strange Celebration
He's really going to
make him a starter
Manager Heo
must be crazy
Yeah, but you never
saw him in college
I heard he was a
big deal back then
But this is different
this is the pro league
I heard he broke
his shoulder too
I met him once in
a fall preseason game
I'd never seen
a pitch like that
I couldn't even swing
Did he throw that fast?
I'd never seen a pitch
so scary in all my life
Take your base!
I had no time to duck
Then the way you
keep forgetting
names and phone numbers...
...that's when it started?
That wasn't all of it
I found out later
The girl he dated backthen
was a fan of mine
So he beaned you
on purpose?
Crazy fool
Cool though, isn't it?
We throw the ball
to get an out
Chi-sung threw
it for love
How hard were
you throwing just now?
At about 80%
Just think of it as
throwing for practice
Maybe next year you can
start again as a pitcher
By next year...
it'll be a new season
Excuse me
Yes, how can I help you?
I came to get
some money...
Excuse me?
I mean, a loan or something...
Club members, prepare yourself
You brought your
stamp and ID card?
A house mortgage
for $100,000?
Yes
On the floor!
Get down!
What the hell's with you?
On the floor!
This freak's got
a death wish!
Get down!
I...
don't have a death wish...
You think that's why
I'm doing this?
I want to live too!
Look, you guys
You... one, two
three, four...
Why are there so damned many?
You nine guys!
Are you a baseball team?
You guys are doing this
in order to live well
But I'm getting a loan
'cause I'm gonna die
You guys are waving guns around
'cause you wanna live
What about me?
I have no choice
but to die!
So I'm mortgaging my home
so what?
You!
Do you know what love is?
But why did you do it
in such a big group?
We heard that once
8 people had done it
We thought we'd try to
set a new record
You talked a lot
with the man
who came for a loan?
We were just listening
Firs the started
talking about the loan
Then what did he start
yelling about?
Something in
black and white?
Then what? He started
going on about love
From then on it was mostly
talk about love
Then I said
what's so great about love?
You meet a woman
ask her name
Once you know her name
you start loving her
Then you ask her age
and her favorite food...
How did you...?
It's a mobile phone
The one I got from
the station
it takes pictures
and the color's nice
I've got money too
I never asked
you for this
And why are you
following me?
- I didn't follow you
- Then how'd you find...?
You asked the
real estate broker!
Damn guy, always telling
people where I live
Why don't you remember me?
My home is just
39 steps from here
it used to be over 60
but now It's just 39
I'm not following you
You told me yourself
and even pointed it out
My mom asked me
to give you this
Oh, you just moved in?
Where is your new home?
Around that corner
the second house on the right
Tell your mom we'll bring
the plate back after we finish
Goodbye
You're really amazing
opening this place
It's just for fun
Okay, stop by sometime
Sure, I live just over there
- Oh really?
- Yeah
- Okay, see you
- I'll come often
- Please do
- Bye then
- Later
- Yeah
Help wanted
Bartender (female)
You came to register
this phone?
Yes
By the way
is this a good phone?
It's the newest model
The most expensive
What phone number
would you like?
Let me think...
Oh, this is
already registered
- Really?
- it has caller ID too
- Hello?
- I...
Forgot to tell you
your phone number
I didn't want you to
go to the agency for nothing
I'm at the agency now
By the way
what are you doing tonight?
- Why?
- Actually...
My postcard was read
at another station too...
A movie?
How many radio stations
did you send it to?
Five stations
And how many chose it?
Five
Do things always
work out so well for you?
I got a 3rd prize Lotto ticket
about three times
she's the female lead
but she dies in the end
is it still interesting
if you know how it ends?
It's too startling
if they die all of a sudden
It's just too sad
The male lead can be sad
but why are you?
And if you know before hand
will you not be sad?
Perhaps so
Oh, I dunno
Better not watch it
Long time no see
How have you been?
Fine
You know my friend?
Oh, sure
Hello
It's been a while
Chi-sung
I thought you
didn't like movies
So you come to
the theater after all...
I got a free ticket
Who's that? Your girlfriend?
No...
Just... someone I know
Really?
Anyway, I'm glad you're well
I was worried
Enjoy the movie
Sure
- Let's go
- Okay
Do you 'just know'
a lot of women?
What?
Are there a lot of women
you 'just know?'
How many?
You're the first
No one else
I'm relieved
What a relief
I feel much better now
The film was about
one woman's love
And about
an old telephone pole
she always stared at
A telephone pole
as the hero
What a weird movie
The man she loved
lived in the city
He used his fists
for cash
earning enough to scrape by
He always thought about
the woman waiting for him
He resisted the temptations
of city women
without his love wavering
in the slightest
Could only happen in a movie
The two loved each other
under the pole
and parted from
each other there
And the old pole
witnessed it all
Even at dawn
as the sun rose
She always waited for him
under the pole
When the sun fell
and it became night
she went home
This tedious movie
finally ended
in a scene where
the man comes back for her
I thought the film was
about his undying love
but it suddenly turned
into an action movie
Damned incoherent film
On top of that
the woman
coughed a few times
and collapsed for no reason
and the man who couldn't
go back also collapsed
in front of him
a strange telephone pole
appeared
He reached out
his hand to the pole
He closed his eyes
thinking about her
And then a strange thing
happened to the telephone pole
His tremendous yearning
for her love
entered the electrical wires
and began to flow
His love passed through
countless poles and wires
making its way to her
And finally
it reached the old pole
where she lay
And our hero the pole
passed on the man's love
To sum up, in aword
love rodethe electrical wires
and reunited our lovers
in this unbearably
stupid movie
Thanks for the movie
and for dinner
And the mobile phone too
Your parents must
be worried, It's late
They passed away
both of them
Mine too
it was the same day
On that neighborhood
club trip
they were on the
same plane
hi, Chi-sung?
It's Dad
We're taking off now
How can such
a big thing like this fly?
Amazing, I tell you
Have a good trip Dad
my game's about to start
Oh, really?
Are you in the
outfield again today?
When are you going to pitch?
You're not gonna
pitch anymore, are you?
Ha...
Now! We're flying now!
The wheels are off
the ground!
What? Now we're
going down again?
Honey, why are
we going down?
- We'll go up again later
- Wait
we're heading
for the ground!
We're gonna hit the ground!
Chi-sung, It's the end
Chi-sung, your father
loves you!
On the first day he flew
he passed away
He took a plane
and went to heaven
Even at his last moment
he told me
that he loved me
You're supposed to turn off
your phone at takeoff
How'd he manage that?
He didn't know
it was his first time!
Goodbye
This trash...
I'll throw it out
at home
Are you looking after Mr. DONG?
Yes
I'm looking after him now
Aword, please
How long has it
been like this?
The two of us, you mean?
No, not that
How long has
he been so sick?
Oh...
I'm not sure
Why, is he very sick?
it has progressed too far
Tastes bitter
Have a candy
Stand by the wall
Move closer
Just a minute
That's fine
What's that?
This is fun
Don't bring me
any more medicine
Thief! Catch him!
Sounds like a thief came
I guess so
Good night, then Bye
Out of the way!
I'll kill you!
I'm not blocking you
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
That's my home
dammit!
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Hey, doing this
at your age?
Why can't you just
work hard and earn money?
Doing this sort of thing
at night is hard work
I can't believe you
Living is hard for me too
But I'd never live
the way you do
Hey, do you know
what love is?
I thought of killing myself too
Rather than live like this
I thought of killing myself
I may be young, but I've
a wife and two kids
So I need to live
If I die
what happens to them?
My life isn't my own
I have to find
some way to get by
Go and live, you punk
Sir!
I'll heed your words
and live well
I'll come visit too
Don't come after two months
I'll be gone
If you move, call me
I'll repay your kindness
I won't be able to call
Live well, don't die
Go on
As for me, I don't know
much about love
But love...
is just love, isn't it?
What kind of love
doesn't matter
If you love, then that's love
But I'm just a thief
so I don't know much
Goodbye
I've nothing to give you
so I'll leave you with that, sir
What are you doing, miss?
What's everyone
doing here?
Do you know
this house's owner?
Why?
What's your relation
with DONG Chi-sung?
I'm just...
a woman he knows
What? Then I'm a detective
he doesn't know
We've found
the stolen item
And also some bundles
of cash
What? is it stolen?
Well, it seems it
might be
For a guy whose shoulder
still isn't 100%
how can he throw that fast?
Just try hitting that
it'll kill you
Don't embarrass me here
just give me something gentle
What is it?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did you do it
you're a nice man
You're not that smart
or good-looking, but
you're nice
Look, what are you
talking about?
How did you end up here?
I asked directions
That's not what I mean
I meant, why are you here?
Let's talk at home
You can't go home!
You can't
They'll catch you if you do
So you don't know
how to contact the thief?
What's the point?
We're being accused
of robbery!
We can't turn him in
he's got a loving wife and kids
Let's just go to the police
and explain everything
Why do you keep saying 'we?'
Go to the station and explain it
Why run away?
I don't have time
Going to the station
and explaining it all
and being dragged from
here to there
I don't have time for that
Are you so busy?
You don't seem
so busy to me
Could I stay at your home
a few days?
Nah, it'll just be
a nuisance
No, It's not that...
I'm fine...
I worry you
might be uncomfortable...
Whatever you want
This room's for sleeping?
You mean the two of us?
No, I asked if you sleep here
You got a language problem...
I sleep here
on the floor
I used to use the bed
but I kept falling off
and hurting myself...
You want to wash up?
I'll go out
and buy something
See how things
are doing outside
is stealing such
a huge crime?
The place is swarming
with cops
You cook well
Try some of this, too
Damn, that's salty
The game's on...
You don't know
baseball at all?
If you get to there
It's one point?
You go to 2nd and 3rd
then come back
Can you run straight from
1st base to 3rd?
No, they'll yell at you
That guy's got much better
is he good?
No
That's not so hard
If you catch
that hit ball...
- The fielder?
- Yes
If the fielder
catches it...
A ground ball?
Yes, if you catch
a ground ball
and chuck it into the crowd
what happens?
- Not to first base?
- Yeah
If you just chuck it
into the crowd
Chuck it...
You can't do that
But, why would
you throw it there?
Just for fun
Can't you?
You can't
You don't know anything
I'd love to see that
That'd be fun
The game's finished
Should I change the channel?
What would you do
if you had two months to live?
What?
Let's say you had
only two months more to live,
what would you do?
Could I die any faster?
What?
Do I have to wait out
the two months?
Could Ijust
get it over with quickly?
It's a pain
waiting two months
with nothing special to do
You're right
Yes, she's correct
Fora person with
two months to live
the biggest agony is
waiting those two months
There isn't
much you can do
to ease that pain
I haven't written a will
Because I have no one
to list in it
I know that my heart
will never withstand this
Not many people
commit suicide by marathon
But It's a clever choice
it won't be too painful
I can think things over
before I die
Today, I'm leaving
this earth
The 5th place prize
was a kimchi refrigerator
This must be
really expensive!
Why'd you buy me this?
I don't have any family...
Thank you
I don't know if
I should accept this...
What should I do?
What do I put in here?
Can I only put in kimchi?
Hey
Are you sleeping?
No, not yet
Come here a minute...
Sit here and listen
You like this song, right?
A long time ago...
When I was in high school
I often heard it while
walking past your window
So I started liking
this song too
Why did you start liking me?
I forget, It's been so long
Do you still like me that much?
You didn't even know I existed
You didn't know
who I was
where I lived
how long and from how close
I could feel your presence
What I liked...
or what I disliked
I'm sorry
For living without knowing
There's a lot I'm doing
for the first time
So...
there's a lot I don't know
It's a thief!
- Hey, you!
- Sir!
Would you like
some tea, or fruit?
- Oh, thank you
- Look, you!
What are you doing
back so soon?
And in the same neighborhood!
You think this is
your workpalce?
Do you commute back
and forth?
Actually, that day I met you
after receiving
your great generosity
I decided to
quit this work
Then why are you
back scaling walls?
Life has fenced me in
Darling, do you know
what love is?
Well...
it would be nice
to buy a computer
hook up the internet
and all that
is that all you can say?
Don't you know?
What love is?
I love you
Should I quit this job?
Sleep when others sleep
work when others work
There's nothing wrong with me
You and the kins...
surely
we can get by
hand to mouth?
- Honey, I...
- You want that too, right?
You don't like staying up
worrying about me?
- Should we tryto live honestly?
- That's great
- but...
- I can cook well
I can try getting a job
at a restaurant
Even with manual labor
we can still feed ourselves, right?
Honey, I...
I'm pregnant again
I'm so sorry, you can't
go home because of me
Forget it, just go
Don't forget your bag
Next time you run away
since you can't go there
hide a tour place
Thank you for
offering, ma'am
I may be nothing
but a petty thief
but I still have moral integrity
You suit each other well!
I don't know what
brought you together
but don't ever part!
You're pigeon-chested
Yes, I've been hearing that
since I was young
So that comes out
in the photo, too
Listen closely
There are two kinds of tumors
Malignant ones
and the gentler ones
Please continue
But this one is malignant
Look here
This here's like that
it shouldn't be like that
If it turns out like that
it won't be good
- Darling!
- Look at this
It's already moved up here
What with all of you
these days?
Moving all over
the place...
But this...
Something's moving
all over the place?
Have we spoken
in this manner before?
What?
You're pigeon-chested
right?
Yes, I'm quite famous
for that
Hello? Darling
It's malignant
I miss you!
We should take action
on this quickly
DONG Chi-sung is hiding
a disease right now
If the capillary in his nose
has grown so weak
then he'll experience
almost constant nosebleeds
If this continues
he could develop
serious anaemia
The surgery takes 20 minutes
he should do it soon
How did this develop?
There are two possible causes
First, stress and fatigue
can bring it on
in people with
inherently weak nose capillaries
The other possibility
is if from early childhood
one utilizes
a part of one's body
to aggressively remove objects
in the nose cavity, it can happen
I think It's the first thing
you mentioned
At first, that's what
everyone wants to believe
Will it take much longer?
is it hard to puton?
Does it fit?
We can change it, if not
I've never worn
anything like this
It's too revealing
I can't wear an undershirt
my stomach will be cold
It's time for your medicine
I'll be pitching
the day after tomorrow
Will you come watch?
Actually...
I wasn't going to
pitch anymore
I just...
Just one last time
I thought...
I'd try taking the mound
Don't pick your nose
Stop, You can't pick
your nose anymore
Yes, well...
Mr. DONG Chi-sung?
Yes?
I'm a policeman
What?
Catch that bastard!
DONG Chi-sung...
A baseball player
Outfield
I'm a pitcher
You know this man?
No, I don't
Why'd you kill
a man you don't know?
We found a handbag
in your room
Inside that bag
was this watch
The watch still
works fine
But the watch's owner is dead
The watch has gone dead too
Chi-sung...
The sun has risen
The sun is up
but if you keep saying
you don't know anything
I'm going to get real angry
I told you
everything I know
There's something
you don't realize
in this room here
you even have to talk about
things you don't know
in this room
ignorant men
become intellectuals
blind men talk about
things they've seen
and deaf men talk about
things they've heard, got it?
What if they're deafand dumb?
Damn, the blood pressure!
Let's try this again
So on the day of the murder
the thief entered
your home
and you reassured him
and sent him home
I don't know if he
went home directly
And the thief
left the bag at your home
so you gave him $2,000
in return
it wasn't some kind
of trade, It's just...
he was having
a hard time, so...
Does that make any sense?
He's got a hard life
so you give him $2,000?
Hey, my life is hard too!
You think I get rich
running around investigating?
I want $2,000 too!
Well, I can give it to you
Go to my home
and under the blanket...
Oh, the blood pressure again!
DONG Chi-sung
You're free to go now
But Chief!
We've identified
the murderer
it was the victim's
girlfriend
But it seems she planned
to commit suicide
Luckily we found her will
She wrote all the details
of the crime in it
We're trying our best
to find her
If she's not dead
we'll catch her soon
Anyway, sorry to have
troubled you
That's the way
this job is sometimes
Try to understand
But why did she do it?
She said she loved
him too much
That happens
with love sometimes
Dying, killing...
Oh, and your doctor
asked us to give you this
Chi-sung
pitch well today
Pitching suits you better
than the outfield
Chief, do you know that guy?
- Good afternoon
- Yes?
- Oh, It's you again
- Yeah...
is DONG Chi-sung here?
That baseball player?
He must be at
the baseball stadium Look...
You're out!
It's been quite
chilly recently
but with the nicer weather
a lot of fans came tonight
Doosan vs Lotte
bottom of the 6th
DONG Chi-sung
is still on the mound
Gong got selected
as one of the players
and he's doing a good job up
to the middle of the 5th
Quite an unexpected
performance from DONG
With Doosan losing
starters to injury
we thought they'd be
using a lot of relievers
This is quite unexpected
If DONG takes them
past the 7th inning
Doosan will
have a chance
Are you okay?
You're over 100 pitches
- Let's bring in the next guy
- No, I...
I just want...
For as long as
I can throw...
I want to throw
And the pitch...
A hit
Oh, it's a hard hit ball
It's going way back
It's still going...
It's over the fence!
It's a 2-run homerun!
It's 2-0, Doosan is ahead
Dong Chi-sung winds up
It's in play!
It's a single
His third pitch, inside
It's a fly ball
Well, I expected KO would
close out the game
but DONG is still in there
Of course it's nice
to pitch a complete game
but they can't afford
to worry about that now
I've spent a long time
asking just what love is
Amazingly
however curious I was
I never looked up the word
in the dictionary
Because I knew
I wouldn't believe
what it said
But what's obvious is
today I'm pitching
for someone special
- It's in play!
- He got it
DONG fielded it on one hop
DONG had a great game today
His second debut in the pros
was a big success
Doosan wins, 2-0
He's not throwing it
This is the last throw
I'll ever make
Now the woman I know
and everyone else
will never forget
this image of me
Goodbye, everyone
I was really curious
If I fielded a ball and
threw it into the crowd
what would happen?
Yes
Did you see it?
You wouldn't believe
the look on the manager's face
What if you
can never play again?
No big deal if I can't
Anyway, come on over
I made dinner
I doubt there will be
any food at your home
so eat here
And the house has been
feeling empty lately
If It's cold out
you can stay the night too
Hello?
Let go, dammit!
Hey, where is that quack?
Are you hiding?
Let go! Don't look at me!
My tumor's moving
all over, is it?
What the hell's moving, huh?
Let go of me!
Where are you?
I mortgaged my house
because of you!
I lost my job!
Hello?
Who?
Oh, boss!
He's over there now?
Get in, I'm gonna
start driving!
All right, all right
Come on, you're drunk
You need to get in first!
Hey, gimme that!
Hey, Yi-yeon
Stop drinking and let's go
Uh, who do we have here?
Our Writing Princess
Get in, we're about to go
Let's go home
Home?
I have no home, dammit
I spent all my damn money!
Got fired from my job!
What?
You gonna let me stay?
At your house?
Why?
Do you love me?
You interested in me?
Why do you do this to me?
Are you not sure?
Why do you talk that way?
Do you really not know?
Are you asking
because you're curious?
Damn, tell me if you love me!
I love you
Don't worry
He'll come back
when he's sober
He can't drink
where'd he pick up
these bad mannerisms?
- I'll be going now
- Huh? Sure
- His bag...
- Huh?
Oh, sure
Sorry, I'm sorry
But I...
I don't know anything
I could'vejust
lived two months
and then died
but why did I have to live?
If I died, I think I could
understand everything
it would be a relief
That would be great
I don't know
Dammit
Does it hurt?
it hit you hard
I'm not sure yet
But have we met before?
You're the woman
from the stadium
So you'll really die?
I guess I will
This is what you wanted
to love and then die
Lucky you
I don't know
Why am I so sad?
What?
It's what you wanted
I guess it wasn't
I guess you can only
feel it when you're alive
Wait a minute
wait
What's so great
about love?
You meet a woman
ask her name
Once you know her name
you start loving her
Then you ask her age
her favorite food...
Love is just... waiting
You can go to it
Love is waiting
for you, go!
Whether it's ball four
or you're hit by a pitch...
I don't know much about love
But love...
is just love, isn't it?
What kind of love
doesn't matter
If you love...
She said
she loved him too much
That happens
with love sometimes
Dying, killing...
I hear you breathing
Your breathing...
So you're alive
I just want to stay here
for as long
as you are alive...
is that okay?
I...
I want to ask you something
What's your name?
Yi-yeon
HAN Yi-yeon
That's pretty
Thank you
So...
Shall I...
escort you home?
My bag...
How old?
Twenty-four
Oh, twenty-four
And your favorite food?
Cup noodles
Ah, noodles
Your hobby?
- Radio
- Right
Right, radio The postcards...
Your blood type is O?
B
People with B
their personality...
nice
I'm type O
Today I received three things
that other people had
and I didn't
I got next year
I got bad mannerisms
and I got first love
Oh, really...
When did you get measles?
- When I was seven
- Oh, seven...
- Your blood type...
- I already told you!
Just now?
- Did I say I'm type O?
- Yes